<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Film n TV</string>

    //Hint FIle
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="date">Date Release</string>
    <string name="genre">Genre</string>

    //TabName
    <string name="TabFilm">Film</string>
    <string name="TabTV">TV</string>
    <string name="production">Production</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>

    //Film
    //Title
    <string-array name="film_title">
        <item>Jumanji</item>
        <item>Godzilla vs Kong</item>
        <item>Tom and Jerry</item>
        <item>Train to Busan: Peninsula</item>
        <item>One Piece: Stampede</item>
        <item>Stand by Me Doraemon 2</item>
        <item>Avatar 2</item>
        <item>Gemini Man</item>
        <item>Tenet</item>
        <item>Wonder Woman 1984</item>
    </string-array>

    //DateRelease
    <string-array name="film_daterelease">
        <item>January, 20 2021</item>
        <item>Maret, 26 2021</item>
        <item>February, 26 2021</item>
        <item>July, 15 2020</item>
        <item>September, 18 2019</item>
        <item>November, 20 2020</item>
        <item>Desember, 16 2022</item>
        <item>October, 2 2019</item>
        <item>August, 22 2020</item>
        <item>Desember, 16 2020</item>
    </string-array>

    //Genre
    <string-array name="film_genre">
        <item>Adventure, Comedy</item>
        <item>Action, Science Fiction</item>
        <item>Comedy, Family, Adventure</item>
        <item>Action, Horror, Thriller</item>
        <item>Animation, Action, Adventure</item>
        <item>Animation</item>
        <item>Action, Adventure, Science Fiction, Fantasy, Thriller</item>
        <item>Science Fiction, Action, Drama, Thriller</item>
        <item>Action, Thriller, Science Fiction</item>
        <item>Fantastic, Action, Adventure</item>
    </string-array>

    //Production
    <string-array name="film_ph">
        <item>Anchors</item>
        <item>Legendary Picture</item>
        <item>Warner Bros</item>
        <item>Redpeter Films</item>
        <item>Toei Animations</item>
        <item>CBI Picture</item>
        <item>20th Century Fox</item>
        <item>Paramount Picture</item>
        <item>Warner bros</item>
        <item>DC</item>
    </string-array>

    //Description
    <string-array name="film_desc">
        <item>Set in 1869, two children receive a mysterious game after their father goes missing in the jungles of Africa. They unravel both the secret of their father’s disappearance and the origin of Jumanji. See how it all began.</item>
        <item>Legends collide as Godzilla and Kong, the two most powerful forces of nature, clash in a spectacular battle for the ages! The monster war rages on the surface and deep within our world as the spectacular secret realm of the titans known as the hollow earth is revealed</item>
        <item>Tom the cat and Jerry the mouse get kicked out of their home and relocate to a fancy New York hotel, where a scrappy employee named Kayla will lose her job if she can\'t evict Jerry before a high-class wedding at the hotel. Her solution? Hiring Tom to get rid of the pesky mouse.</item>
        <item>A soldier and his team battle hordes of post-apocalyptic zombies in the wastelands of the Korean Peninsula.</item>
        <item>One Piece: Stampede is a stand-alone film that celebrates the anime\'s 20th Anniversary and takes place outside the canon of the "One Piece" TV series. Monkey D. Luffy and his Straw Hat pirate crew are invited to a massive Pirate Festival that brings many of the most iconic characters from throughout the franchise to participate in competition with the Straw Hats to find Roger\'s treasure. It also pits the Straw Hats against a new enemy named Bullet, a former member of Roger\'s crew.</item>
        <item>She and her beloved Shizuka are finally married! Nobita\'s childhood dream was supposed to come true on his wedding day, but for some reason, Nobita doesn\'t show up. One of the most popular episodes from the original story transcends time and space, and leads to Nobita\'s future. Doraemon and Nobita\'s great adventure begins in order to fulfill his grandmother\'s wish to see his bride at first sight. This is a story of tears and bonds, set in the past, present and future.</item>
        <item>Avatar: The Way of Water will once again follow Sam Worthington\’s Jake Sully twelve years after exploring Pandora and joining the Na\’vi. He has since raised a family with Neytiri, portrayed by Zoe Saldana, and established himself within the clans of the new world. Of course, peace can only last so long. Especially when the military organisation from the original film returns to “finish what they started”.</item>
        <item>Henry Brogan is an elite 51-year-old assassin who\'s ready to call it quits after completing his 72nd job. His plans get turned upside down when he becomes the target of a mysterious operative who can seemingly predict his every move. To his horror, Brogan soon learns that the man who\'s trying to kill him is a younger, faster, cloned version of himself.</item>
        <item>Armed with only one word - Tenet - and fighting for the survival of the entire world, the Protagonist journeys through a twilight world of international espionage on a mission that will unfold in something beyond real time.</item>
        <item>Wonder Woman comes into conflict with the Soviet Union during the Cold War in the 1980s and finds a formidable foe by the name of the Cheetah.</item>
    </string-array>

    //Img
    <array name="img_film">
        <item>@drawable/jumanji</item>
        <item>@drawable/godzilla</item>
        <item>@drawable/tomnjerry</item>
        <item>@drawable/peninsula</item>
        <item>@drawable/onepiece</item>
        <item>@drawable/doraemon</item>
        <item>@drawable/avatar</item>
        <item>@drawable/geminiman</item>
        <item>@drawable/tenet</item>
        <item>@drawable/ww</item>
    </array>


    //TV
    //Title
    <string-array name="tv_title">
        <item>Alice in Borderland</item>
        <item>Sweet Home</item>
        <item>Demon Slayer: Kimetsu no Yaiba</item>
        <item>Haikyuu!!</item>
        <item>Haikyuu!!: To The Top</item>
        <item>Jujutsu Kaisen</item>
        <item>Mushoku Tensei: Jobless Reincarnation</item>
        <item>Attack on Titan: The Final Season</item>
        <item>2.43: Seiin High School Boys Volleyball Team</item>
        <item>WandaVision</item>
    </string-array>

    //DateRelease
    <string-array name="tv_daterelease">
        <item>December, 10 2020</item>
        <item>December, 18 2020</item>
        <item>April, 6 2019</item>
        <item>April, 6 2014</item>
        <item>January, 11 2020</item>
        <item>October, 3 2020</item>
        <item>January, 11 2021</item>
        <item>December, 7 2020</item>
        <item>January, 8 2021</item>
        <item>January, 15 2021</item>
    </string-array>

    //Genre
    <string-array name="tv_genre">
        <item>Drama, Mystery, Action and Adventure</item>
        <item>Drama, Sci-Fi and Fantasy</item>
        <item>Animation, Drama, Sci-Fi, Fantasy, Action and Adventure</item>
        <item>Animation, Comedy, Drama</item>
        <item>Animation, Comedy, Drama</item>
        <item>Animation, Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi and Fantasy</item>
        <item>Animation, Drama, Comedy, Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi and Fantasy</item>
        <item>Animation, Sci-Fi, Fantasy, Action, Adventure, Drama, War, Politics and Mystery</item>
        <item>Animation, Drama</item>
        <item>Sci-Fi, Fantasy, Action, Adventure, Mystery and Comedy</item>
    </string-array>

    //Production
    <string-array name="tv_ph">
        <item>Netflix</item>
        <item>Netflix</item>
        <item>Ufotable</item>
        <item>TV Tokyo</item>
        <item>TV Tokyo</item>
        <item>Mappa</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Mappa</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Marvel Studios</item>
    </string-array>

    //Description
    <string-array name="tv_desc">
        <item>With his two friends, a video-game-obsessed young man finds himself in a strange version of Tokyo where they must compete in dangerous games to win.</item>
        <item>Cha Hyun-Soo is a high school student. He is also a recluse and rarely leaves his room. He refuses to talk to his father, mother and younger sister. One day, his whole family, except for him, dies in a car accident. Cha Hyun-Soo is left all alone. He moves into a small apartment. At this time, a mysterious phenomenon of humans turning into monster occur all around the world. The residents of Cha Hyun-Soo\'s apartment building, including Pyeon Sang-Wook, fight against these monsters and try to survive.</item>
        <item>It is the Taishō period in Japan. Tanjirō, a kindhearted boy who sells charcoal for a living, finds his family slaughtered by a demon. To make matters worse, his younger sister Nezuko, the sole survivor, has been transformed into a demon herself. Though devastated by this grim reality, Tanjirō resolves to become a “demon slayer” so that he can turn his sister back into a human, and kill the demon that massacred his family.</item>
        <item>Shōyō Hinata was inspired to play volleyball after seeing Kurasuno High School\'s "little giant" competing in the national tournament on TV. He trains relentlessly to make up for his lack of height, but suffers a crushing defeat in his first and last tournament of middle school at the hands of his rival Tobio Kageyama. Vowing revenge against Kageyama and hoping to follow in the little giant\'s footsteps, Hinata joins Kurasuno High School\'s volleyball team. To his initial dismay, Kageyama is also on Kurasuno\'s team. The former rivals soon overcome their differences though and combine their strengths to form a legendary combo using Hinata\'s mobility and Kageyama\'s precision ball-handling. Together with their team, they compete in prefecture tournaments and promise to meet Kurasuno\'s fated rival school at nationals.</item>
        <item>After their triumphant victory over Shiratorizawa Academy, the Karasuno High School volleyball team has earned their long-awaited ticket to nationals. As preparations begin, genius setter Tobio Kageyama is invited to the All-Japan Youth Training Camp to play alongside fellow nationally recognized players. Meanwhile, Kei Tsukishima is invited to a special rookie training camp for first-years within the Miyagi Prefecture. Not receiving any invitations himself, the enthusiastic Shouyou Hinata feels left behind. However, Hinata does not back down. Transforming his frustration into self-motivation, he boldly decides to sneak himself into the same rookie training camp as Tsukishima. Even though Hinata only lands himself a job as the ball boy, he comes to see this as a golden opportunity. He begins to not only reflect on his skills as a volleyball player but also analyze the plethora of information available on the court and how he can apply it.</item>
        <item>Yuuji Itadori is a boy with tremendous physical strength, though he lives a completely ordinary high school life. One day, to save a friend who has been attacked by Curses, he eats a finger of Ryoumen Sukuna, taking the Curse into his own soul. From then on, he shares one body with Sukuna. Guided by the most powerful of sorcerers, Satoru Gojou, Itadori is admitted to the Tokyo Prefectural Jujutsu High School, an organization that fights the Curses and thus begins the heroic tale of a boy who became a Curse to exorcise a Curse, a life from which he could never turn back.</item>
        <item>34-year-old virgin loser is kicked out of his home by his family and realized that his life is completely over. As he regrets wasting his life, a truck runs him over and he died. When he wakes up. He\’s in a world of sword and sorcery! Reborn as a baby named Rudeus, he decides that this time, he\’ll live a life he won\’t regret!</item>
        <item>The truth revealed through the memories of Grisha\'s journals shakes all of Eren\'s deepest beliefs. There is no rugged but free land beyond the walls. There is a whole other world, equally full of oppression and war. Suddenly, the ambitions that have animated the Survey Corps for generations seem small and naive. What is there left to fight for?</item>
        <item>Kimichika Haijima was a strong junior high school volleyball team member. After getting into trouble with the team, he moved to his mother\'s hometown and reunites with his childhood friend, Yuni Kuroba. The two become an ace pair at volleyball, but in their last tournament, get into a big fight. Will they ever play volleyball together again?</item>
        <item>Wanda Maximoff and Vision—two super-powered beings living idealized suburban lives—begin to suspect that everything is not as it seems.</item>
    </string-array>

    //Img
    <array name="img_tv">
        <item>@drawable/aliceinborderland</item>
        <item>@drawable/sweethome</item>
        <item>@drawable/kny</item>
        <item>@drawable/haikyuu</item>
        <item>@drawable/haikyuuttt</item>
        <item>@drawable/jujutsu</item>
        <item>@drawable/mushokutensei</item>
        <item>@drawable/aot</item>
        <item>@drawable/seiin</item>
        <item>@drawable/wanda</item>
    </array>

</resources>